People think I don't care.
Oh, I kind of thought you didn't care.
Who doesn't care?
I'm a comedian, an actress, an only child, and a girl.
I fucking care.
Amanda Steele.
Amanda Steele!
My special came out on HBO.
I was on a show on NBC.
I think because I am so outwardly and vocally
critical of the world, people look at me like,
well, then you better be perfect.
Some people will try and call you angry
to diminish the value of what you're saying.
Right.
When you left the real, it was your last-ditch effort
of being like, I can be part of the system.
You do see me.
I think so.
I thought these are my people.
They're not my people.
But this idea that, like, my merit as a person
is based on whether or not these other people liked me.
We came here to have a good time and celebrate today.
How much dating went on on the insecure set?
I don't even think people know that I dated somebody on insecure.
I dated .
Really?
Yeah.
You're producing a stand-up special.
It's not your traditional special.
It is completely 100% independent.
I am the star and I am the financier.
I'm running to the people.
Ooh.
I am the star and I am the star.
I'm the star.
I am the star.